Guide to the Anne Ramsay Somers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1961-1977; Series II; 6 linear feet (12 boxes)
  - Speeches and Shorter Writings
    - "Developing a Program in Community Health Education: One Hospital's Experience," with William, Vaun, Prism: copies of article and correspondence, 1973 December (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - "The Hospital as a Management System: From Responsiblity to Accountability," Harvey H. Weiss Memorial Lecture, Maryland-Delaware-Virginia-D.C. Hospital Association: text and agenda, 1974 January 6-7 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - National Academy of Sciences, Institute of Medicine, Conference on Regulation in the Health Industry: correspondence and notes, 1974 January 7-9 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, Symposium on the Costs of Medical Education: correspondence and notes, 1974 January 11 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - "Lifestyle, Death Rates and Some Implications for National Health Insurance," Veteran's Administration, East Orange: working copy of text, 1974 January 18 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - American Association of Medical Colleges Regional Meeting: correspondence and agenda, 1974 February 13-14 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - "Educating the Consumer," New Jersey Hospital Association: copies, 1974 February (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, "V.D. Hotline," correspondence and text, 1974 April 11 (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - "Medical Manpower Needs of Vermont," University of Vermont College of Medicine: correspondence, 1974 April 25-26 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, review of David Rutstein's: correspondence and review, 1974 May 16 (Box 15, Folder 180)
    - "Consumer Health Education: A New Opportunity for the Hospital and the Medical Staff," American Medical Association News: correspondence, text and reviews, 1974 May 27 (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - "National Health Insurance: An Incomplete Drama," Blue Cross of Northeast Ohio, Cleveland: correspondence and text, 1974 May 30-31 (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - Cornell University Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Sloan Institute summer development program: correspondence and speech notes, 1974 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - "Public Contribution and Participation in P.S.R.O.," Private Initiative in P.S.R.O., Lake Geneva (Wisconsin): speech text and notes, 1974 July 8 (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - "Remarks on Receipt of Honorary Fellowship in the American College of Hospital Administrators," Chicago: speech text and correspondence, 1974 August 11 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - "Recharting National Health Priorities: A New Canadian Perspective," New England Journal of Medicine: text, correspondence and editorial response, 1974 August 22 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - "The General Trend to Public Accountability," U.S.D.H.E.W., Health Insurance Benefits Advisory Council, and National Professional Standards Review Council, Washington, D.C.: speech text and notes, 1974 September 10 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - American Medical News: interview (Box 16, Folder 188)
    - "Consumer Health Education: A New Opportunity for the Hospital and the Medical Staff," Mercer Hospital, Trenton: correspondence and speech draft, 1974 October 24 (Box 16, Folder 189)
    - "Health Education and Behavior Modification; The Challenge to Task Force IV," National Institutes of Health and American College of Preventive Medicine, Chicago: opening remarks and question list, 1974 November 12 (Box 16, Folder 190)
    - "A State-Wide Health Education Program in Action," Blue Cross Association Seminar on Health Education, New York: notes and conference material, 1974 November 26 (Box 16, Folder 191)
    - "Technology, Bureaucracy and Health Care: The Sorcerer's Apprentice Revisited," American Association for the Advancement of Science, New York: correspondence and speech text, 1975 January 29 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    - "Home Care: Much Needed, Much Neglected," Annals of Internal Medicine: editorial text and correspondence, 1975 January (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - "Recharting National Health Priorities," Health Industry Manufacturers Association: speech notes, 1975 February 3 (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - "Consumer Health Education: An Idea Whose Time Has Come?" Hospital Progress, Journal of the Catholic Hospital Association: paper text, 1975 February (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - "Home Care: A Nursing Home Alternative," The New York Times: letter to the editor and correspondence, 1975 March 1 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - "Consumer Health Education," (South Carolina): speech text, 1975 March 18 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - "The Role of the Consumer In Health Care Planning," Greensville (South Carolina): speech text, 1975 March 19 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - "Community Participation in Effective Hospital Operations," Greensville, (South Carolina): speech text, correspondence and program, 1975 March 20 (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - "Community Participation in Effective Hospital Operations," American College Health Association, New York: speech text and program, 1975 April 3 (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - Rutgers University College of Pharmacy, New Jersey: notes and correspondence, 1975 April 9 (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - New Jersey Welfare Council: program and notes, 1975 April 30-May 1 (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - "Lifestyle and Health Status: the Challenge to Health Education," New York University Medical Center: correspondence, text and notes, 1975 May 13 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - To Know--or Die: The Challenge to Consumer Health Education, Pittsburgh: text, and correspondence, 1975 May 21 (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - "Lifestyle Related Illness: Challenge to the Class of 1975," Medical College of Wisconsin: speech, correspondence and program, 1975 May 25 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Community Hospital Services: Public Demands--Appropriate Response--Finding the Balance, Vermont Hospital Association: text and notes, 1975 May 28 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - "Hospital Based Consumer Education," with William Vaun, Association for Hospital Medical Education Journal: correspondence, draft and tear sheet, 1975 May (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - "The Malpractice Crisis, Patient Education and the Doctor-Patient Relationship," University of Oregon Health Sciences Center: correspondence, text and clippings, 1975 June 13 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - "Issues in the Structure and Administration of State Health Cost Regulations," with Lawrence Lewin and Herman Somers, Toledo Law Review: text, 1975 June (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - "National Guidelines for the Health Planning and Resources Development Act," with Herman Somers, United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: correspondence and background material, 1975 August-1977 August (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Philadelphia College of Physicians: notes and reference material, 1975 September 16 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - "Trends in Health Economics and the Delivery of Health Care," International Health Advisory Council and Booz, Allen and Hamilton, Inc.: notes and clippings, 1975 September 26 (Box 17, Folder 212)
    - Planned Parenthood--World Population, Center for Family Planning Program Development: correspondence, pamplhets and tear sheet, 1975 October 2-3 (Box 17, Folder 213)
    - "The Philadelphia Medical Commons: Mounting the Guard," Philadelphia Health Management Corporation: notes, text and correspondence, 1975 October 15 (Box 17, Folder 214)
    - "Consumer Health Education: A New Challenge to the Medical Profession," Medical Association of Georgia: text, correspondence and reprints, 1975 November 21 (Box 17, Folder 215)
    - "The Organization and Financing of Patient Education Programs, with Special Reference to Diabetes," American Diabetes Association (Atlanta): text and correspondence, 1975 November 22 (Box 17, Folder 216)
    - "Responsiblities of Health Care Managers in 1980," Canadian College of Hospital Administrators, Quebec: text, correspondence and conference material, 1975 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 217)
    - "State Health Cost Regulation: Structure and Administration," Toledo Law Review article: correspondence, 1976 February (Box 17, Folder 218)
    - "How Are We Going to Pay Our Medical Bills?" Twentieth Century Club, Pittsburgh: text and notes, 1976 March 1 (Box 17, Folder 219)
    - "The Patient Package Insert for Prescription Drugs, as a Tool for Consumer Health Education," New Jersey Health Sciences Group: text and correspondence, 1976 March 2 (Box 17, Folder 220)
    - Public Affairs Committee, Inc., Search for Solutions Conference, New York: notes and correspondence, 1976 March 31 (Box 17, Folder 221)
    - "Violence, Television, and the Health of American Youth," New England Journal of Medicine: correspondence, text and drafts, 1976 April 8 (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - "Educating the Consumer: It Can Mean Better Health," American Medical Association, Phoenix: correspondence and text, 1976 April 9 (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - "Geriatric Care in the United Kingdom: An American Perspective," Annals of Internal Medicine: correspondence, text and reprints, 1976 April (Box 17, Folder 224)
    - "An Approach to U.S. Health Policy for the Late Seventies," Hospital Research and Development Institute, Inc., Tampa (Florida): text, correspondence and notes, 1976 May 5 (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - National Academy of Sciences, Institute of Medicine, Conference on Care of the Elderly: correspondence, 1976 May 17-18 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - "Health Education Should be Part of Total Patient Care," American Hospital Association: article draft, 1976 May (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - "Negotiated Rates: One Road to Mutual Responsibility and Cost Containment in Health Care," American Board of Medical Specialties: text, 1977 September 15 (Box 17, Folder 228)
- Project Files, 1966-1979; Series III; 1.5 linear feet (3 boxes)
  Series III is arranged alphabetically by organization name or project title.
  - American Board of Medical Specialties: correspondence and notes, 1974-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - American Diabetes Association, Health Education Project
    - Correspondence, reports and notes, 1974-1976 August (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - Booz, Allen and Hamilton, Inc.
    - Correspondence and reports, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "The Public Policy Rationale for Regulation and Control," speech text, 1972 October 13 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Duke University Medical Center Board of Visitors: correspondence and related material, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Excerpta Medica: correspondence and pamphlets, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - First International Conference on Patient Counselling: correspondence and conference material, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Health Facilities Planning Council for New Jersey: memoranda and administrative papers, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Healthy America, The National Coalition for Health Promotion: correspondence and promotional material, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hunterdon Medical Center, Special Health Education Project: correspondence, pamphlets and clippings, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Massey (Jack C.) Foundation Award Selection Committee: correspondence, clippings and announcements, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - New Jersey, Committee to Study the Structure and Function of the Health Department: correspondence, notes and report, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey Department of Health: correspondence, clippings and related material, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Medicine Today--Its Assets and Liabilities, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Prescription: A Series of Seven Television Shows Spotlighting New Health and Hospital Programs in New Jersey
    - Script and proposal outlines, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence re: fund raising and financial agreements, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Princeton University, Colloquia on Major Public Policy Issues in Financing and Delivery of Health Care: correspondence, clippings and speech text, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Princeton University, proposal to establish a Center for International Studies in Health Care Administration: memoranda, correspondence, and reference material, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Project Hope, The People-to-People Health Foundation, Inc.: correspondence, project proposals and related material, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Proposal for television series: correspondence proposal drafts and notes, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Proposal re: state regulation of hospitals: correspondence and articles, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    - National Council on Health Planning and Development: correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - National Institutes of Health
      - Expert Panel on Consumer Health Education
        - General correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 24)
        - Reports, correspondence and related material, 1976 February 5-6 (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence, reference material and recommendations, 1976 June 24-26 (Box 20, Folder 26)
        - Reference material, 1976 June (Box 20, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, 1976 December 16-17 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - National Conference on Preventive Medicine: correspondence, 1975 June 9-11 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Task Force IV on Consumer Health Education: correspondence, notes and related material, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Social Security Administration, Health Insurance Benefits Advisory Council: correspondence and reports, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Woman M.D.: correspondence, reports and article, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Additional Material, 1975-1981; Accession 1984-M-007; 5 linear feet (12 boxes)
  Preliminary inventory by Robert Raffeld 1984 Jul
  Ms. Gr. No. 1237
  Received from: Anne R. Somers, 23 Nov 1983
  - Reissman Conference, 1975 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ginzburg project, 1975 October 1-1978 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - PIPSRO-ADA research project proposal, 1975 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Homemaker-Home Health Aide Services article, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Public Health Reports-VD Hotline, 1976 May - June (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hospital Research and Development Institute, 1976 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1976 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annals of Internal Medicine editorial on Violence, 1976 June (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Internal Medicine, 1976 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Medical Economics article, 1976 September (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fielding meeting, 1976 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Harvard School of Public Health, 1976 September 15-17 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Board of Medical Specialties, 1976 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American College of Preventive Medicine, 1976 October (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hospital Progress article, 1976 October (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Joslin Diabetes Foundation, 1976 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Public Health Association, 1976 October 19-20 (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
  - Institute of Medicine meeting, 1976 October 26-28 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Center for Biomedical Education, 1976 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Board of Medical Specialties, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Health and Health Care, book, 1977 January - April 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26-28)
  - Georgia Health Promotion Conference, 1977 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Blue Cross Association Conference, 1977 January 16-19 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Pennsylvania Dept. of Health, 1977 January 2 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - American Society of Preventive Oncology, 1977 February 5 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - PTA public hearing on TV violence and its effect on children, 1977 February 15 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Office of Health Information and Health Promotion, 1977 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - University of Pennsylvania Colloquium, 1977 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Office of Consumer Health Education, 1977 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Raritan Valley Chamber of Commerce, 1977 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - New England Journal of Medicine article, 1977 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Requests for reprints of NEJM article (Box 3, Folder 39-41)
  - Walt Disney - Johns Hopkins conference, 1977 March 18-19 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - U.S. Army - Baylor University, 1977 March 28 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1977 April 28 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Roosevelt Hospital, 1977 April 29 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - American Psychiatric Association, 1977 May 2 (Box 4, Folder 46-47)
  - Bergen Pines Hospital, 1977 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Inquiry article, 1977 June (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Federal Trade Commission Conference, 1977 June 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
  - Group Health Association of America, 1977 June 20-21 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Canadian Public Health Association, 1977 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Aspen book permissions, 1977 August - December (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Pennsylvania Health Conference, 1977 August 1 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Preventive Medicine article, 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Canadian Journal of Public Health article, 1977 September - October (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Dept. of National Health and Welfare, Ottawa, 1977 September 6 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - American Board of Medical Specialties, 1977 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Duke Special Seminar, 1977 September 20 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Columbia University Arden House Conference, 1977 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - The Internist article, 1977 October (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Society of Teachers of Family Medicine, 1977 October - December (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - University of Missouri, 1977 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Colorado Medical Care and Research Foundation, 1977 October 6 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - University of Colorado Medical School, 1977 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Digestive Diseases Testimony, 1977 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Institute of Medicine, 1977 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - University of Tennessee lecture, 1977 November 1 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Princeton University Speech, 1977 November 15 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Abortion letter to N.Y. Times, 1977 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Consumer Health Educators, 1977 December 7 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Rockefeller Award lunch, 1977 December 8 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Hahnemann Medical College, 1977 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - American Alliance for Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1978 January 2 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Blue Cross Conference on Health Care, 1978 January 17 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Hospitals article, 1978 February 1 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - UCSF Conference on Aging, 1978 February 24 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Duke Council on Aging, 1978 March (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Journal of Family Practice article, 1978 March (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Philadelphia College of Physicians, 1978 March 1 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Jersey Shore Medical Center, 1978 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Danbury Hospital, 1978 March 20 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - New Jersey Medical School, 1978 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Mercer Company Cancer Society, 1978 March 23 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - New England Journal of Medicine editorial, 1978 March 30 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - American Orthopsychiatric Association, 1978 April (Box 6, Folder 87-88)
  - University of Connecticut Medical School, 1978 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Rutgers MPA Association, 1978 April 27 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Journal of the Medical Society of New Jersey, 1978 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - New York Academy at Medicine, 1978 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Washington National Journal Conference, 1978 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Fresno Conference, 1978 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 94-95)
  - Inquiry commentary, 1978 June (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Lancaster General Hospital, 1978 June 8 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - New York State Public Health Association, 1978 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Health Systems Agency, 1978 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - College of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - International Seminar on health education Tokyo, Japan, 1978 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 101-102)
  - Seminar Associates, 1978 September 27 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Forum article, 1978 October (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Diabetes Care editorial, 1978 October (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - WNET, 1978 October 1 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Duke Private Sector Conference, 1978 October 2 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - New Jersey Health Officers Association, 1978 November 15 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Rutgers Social Work Seminar, 1978 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Princeton University Seminar, 1978 October 20 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - People's Independent Coalition, 1978 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Army - Baylor University, 1979 January 16 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Containment of Health Care Costs Forum, 1979 February (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - HSA meeting, 1979 February 3 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - New England Journal of Medicine, editorial, 1979 February 8 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - American Association of Retired Persons Conference, 1979 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Medical Economics article, 1979 March 19 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Union College, 1979 March 22 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Greater Cleveland Hospital Association, 1979 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Duke Conference, 1979 April 9 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - University of Northern Colorado, 1979 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - New England Journal of Medicine editorial, 1979 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Pennsylvania Medical Society, 1979 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - "Marital Status" article, 1979 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - J. Hamburg article, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - The Pharos article, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Hartford Hospital, 1979 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Hackensack Hospital, 1979 May 4 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Health Officers lecture, 1979 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Blue Cross Conference, 1979 June (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Veterans Administration Conference, 1979 September 11 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Conference on Charging Values in Medicine, 1979 November 11-13 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Inquiry article, 1980 Spring (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Cornell Medical College, 1980 February 13 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Hospital Association of DC, MD, VA, 1980 March 13 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - National Health Council, 1980 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Wayne State University, 1980 April 11-12 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - New Jersey Gerontological Society, 1980 April 24 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1980 May 1 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Penn State University, 1980 May 14 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Hospitals article, 1980 May 16 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Duke Private Sector Conference, 1980 May 24 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - University of Texas, 1980 June 7 (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Institute of Medicine Conference on Health Promotion, 1980 June 10 (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - Mississippi Hospital Association, 1980 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Fry book, 1980 August (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Hospital Progress article, 1980 August (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Institute of Medicine Conference, 1980 September 9 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Blue Cross of Philadelphia, 1980 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Last Project, 1980 October (Box 10, Folder 151-152)
  - Institute of Medicine meeting, 1980 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - University of Rochester Colloquium on Aging, 1980 October 22 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Michigan State University speech, 1980 October 31 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Regional Health Planning Council Conference, 1980 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - U.C.S.F. Conference on Aging, 1980 November 15-16 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Home Care Conference, 1980 November 23 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Patient Care interview, 1981 January 15 (Box 10, Folder 159)